Keli Elizabeth Rice

I am a Creative Designer with an educational and professional background that spans architecture, user experience design, and human-computer interaction design in complex technical environments. My favorite design problems exist where technology meets space, and my diverse background helps me bridge the gaps that my clients often encounter.

Experience

2024-PRESENT

Technology Systems Designer

Hammel, Green, and Abrahamson (HGA)

Experience Consultations | Facility-Integrated Technology Design Developing AV Models and Diagrams | Process Development Construction Documents | System Evaluation

2017-2024

Director of UX/UI Design

Professional Audio Design

UI Designer for AV Systems | Front-End Development User Training | Establishing UX Design Processes Brand Stewardship | System Evaluation and Planning

2014-2017

Architectural Assistant

University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee

Project Manager for Campus Signage | Graphic Design Manage Campus Planning Website | Promote Capital Projects Maintain Facility Database | Event Coordination

Interests

User Centered Design | Collaborative Project Approach | User Training Interaction Design | Rapid Prototyping | Information Sciences Cross Directional Mentorship | Diagramming and Iterative Design

Electronic Exhibits | Rock Climbing | Cycling | Community Science

Education

BS Architecture - University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee

Two-Dimensional Design | Greening Milwaukee | Architecture & Human Behavior | Virtual Modeling | Sustainable Architecture of the 21st Century

CONTACT ME

kelirice.com hello@kelirice.com linkedin.com/in/kelirice instagram.com/ktrocity/

NOTEWORTHY WORK

Lindemann Center **Brown University**

Milwaukee Symphony Orchestra **Bradley Symphony Center**

Emergency Department Froedtert Hospital

Corporate Headquarters **Duluth Trading Company**

Various Hearing Rooms
Wisconsin State Capitol

TECHNICAL SKILLS

InDesign, Illustrator, Figma Rhino, Revit, AutoCAD Clip Studio, Photoshop VS Code, GitHub

CERTIFIED STUDY

AV Mathematics (AVIXA)
UX Design (Coursera)
QSYS Level I (QSC)
Dante Level III (Audinate)